<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Article: Transfer Pricing in InnerSource with Cost Contribution Agreements</title><link>/blog/2022/06/article-transfer-pricing-in-innersource-with-cost-contribution-agreements/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/blog/2022/06/article-transfer-pricing-in-innersource-with-cost-contribution-agreements/</guid><description>by Maximilian Capraro &amp; Michael Dorner Together with our partners at TC &amp;amp; P GmbH, we published an article on transfer pricing in InnerSource using cost contribution agreements:
Oliver Treidler, Tom-Eric Kunz, Maximilian Capraro, Michael Dorner (2022). Sustaining arm’s length cost allocations for highly integrated development functions – an explorative case study of transfer pricing for InnerSource communities. MNETAX. Please find the full text directly on mnetax.com and reach out to us with any questions.</description></item><item><title>Company - About Us</title><link>/company/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 16:38:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>/company/</guid><description>Kolabri helps you to adopt, measure, and govern InnerSource in your organization.
Maximilian Capraro Dr. Maximilian Capraro is a co-founder of Kolabri, where he helps companies kick-start and scale their InnerSource programs.
Max is member and assistant treasurer of the InnerSource Commons Foundation and served two terms on its board of directors. He is a (part-time) engineer at DATEV eG where he educates on InnerSource and co-founded one of the firm&amp;rsquo;s most successful InnerSource projects.</description></item><item><title>From Zero to InnerSource</title><link>/services/from-zero-to-innersource/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 16:37:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>/services/from-zero-to-innersource/</guid><description>Adopting and scaling InnerSource is not a trivial task: Many companies we worked with are uncertain how and where to start. We have worked on InnerSource for nearly a decade: Currently, we are condensing this experience into our turn-key pipeline for helping you adopt, scale, and govern InnerSource: We call it From Zero to InnerSource.
With our From Zero to InnerSource pipeline, we will offer you just the right service packages to not only get your company started with InnerSource but also sustainably scale InnerSource collaboration across the whole company and hundreds of projects.</description></item><item><title>Imprint / Impressum</title><link>/imprint/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 16:37:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>/imprint/</guid><description>Kolabri is a consulting offering provided by Capraro Dorner Softwareingenieure Partnerschaft. The following information is required for websites operated by German organizations or organizations doing business within Germany. Hence, it is written in German.
Angaben gemäß § 5 TMG Capraro Dorner Softwareingenieure Partnerschaft, Saarlandstraße 2, 92318 Neumarkt (in der Oberpfalz) Partnerschaftsregister: PR 316 Registergericht: Amtsgericht Nürnberg Vertreten durch Dr. Maximilian Capraro Michael Dorner Kontakt Telefon: +49 (0) 151 24034251 E-Mail: mail@caprarodorner.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Assessment</title><link>/services/assessment/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 16:37:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>/services/assessment/</guid><description>Assessing your InnerSource program gives you a fresh perspective: What can be improved? Where are the chances and risks that you overlooked? We offer a variety of consulting packages focussing on auditing practices in your InnerSource program, specific projects, or focusing on existing collaboration and contribution-flow in your firm.
Package: InnerSource Program Audit During the audit of your InnerSource program, we carefully inspect your program&amp;rsquo;s practices, elements, mechanisms, and challenges and compare them to known and proven best practices.</description></item><item><title>Transfer Pricing &amp; InnerSource</title><link>/services/transfer-pricing-and-innersource/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 16:37:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>/services/transfer-pricing-and-innersource/</guid><description>InnerSource leads to fine-grained development collaboration - across development silos but also across international borders. We offer multiple service packages to help you comply with necessary taxation regulations while not introducing impediments to InnerSource.
Package: Introductory Workshop During our introductory workshop, we walk you through the foundations of transfer pricing and the arm’s length principle relevant to InnerSource and software engineering.
The workshop delivers:
understanding of key concepts of transfer pricing overview of risks and solutions for transfer pricing in InnerSource joint language to discuss transfer pricing with your stakeholders Package: Advanced Workshop With the advanced workshop, you are at the steering wheel: We will prepare the workshop tailor-made - focusing in-depth on your specific requirements, concerns, and needs regarding transfer pricing and InnerSource.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 16:36:21 +0200</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description>Reach out to us anytime - we look forward to hearing from you.
Kolabri by Capraro Dorner Softwareingenieure PartG Saarlandstraße 2 92318 Neumarkt i. d. Opf. Germany mail@kolabri.io</description></item></channel></rss>