<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Company - About Us on Transfer Pricing for Software Companies</title><link>/company/</link><description>Recent content in Company - About Us on Transfer Pricing for Software Companies</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 16:38:22 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/company/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dr. Maximilian Capraro</title><link>/company/maximilian-capraro/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/company/maximilian-capraro/</guid><description>Dr. Maximilian Capraro is a co-founder of Kolabri, where he helps companies to implement transfer pricing strategies for their globally distributed software engineering.
Max is member and assistant treasurer of the InnerSource Commons Foundation and served two terms on its board of directors. He is a (part-time) engineer at DATEV eG where he educates on InnerSource and co-founded one of the firm&amp;rsquo;s most successful InnerSource projects.
Back in academia, Max performed over six years of research on InnerSource and consulted companies including Siemens, Continental, and Black Duck Software.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Oliver Treidler</title><link>/company/oliver-treidler/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/company/oliver-treidler/</guid><description>Dr. Oliver Treidler (born 1980) studied Business in Stuttgart, Germany from 2002 to 2005. In 2008 he obtained the MSc in International Economics and European Studies at Corvinus University of Budapest. From 2010 to 2013 he completed his Ph.D. in Economics at the University of Wuerzburg.
From 2002 to 2006 Oliver completed an apprenticeship as an airline professional (Luftverkehrskaufmann) and worked in the accounting department of Deutsche Lufthansa AG as well as in the Budapest Field Office (until 2008).</description></item><item><title>Michael Dorner</title><link>/company/michael-dorner/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/company/michael-dorner/</guid><description>Michael Dorner is a co-founder of Kolabri, where he helps companies to implement transfer pricing strategies for their globally distributed software engineering.
Michael holds a researcher position at Blekinge Institute of Technology (BTH) in Sweden. In a prior life, he worked as a data scientist and software developer in Siemens Healthcare. In his work, Michael focuses on leveraging software development simulation and data analytics to understand how developers communicate and collaborate - which is also the theoretical backbone for his pragmatic consulting on InnerSource and software engineering.</description></item><item><title>Tom-Eric Kunz</title><link>/company/tom-eric-kunz/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/company/tom-eric-kunz/</guid><description>Tom is a co-founder of Kolabri, where he helps companies to implement transfer pricing strategies for their globally distributed software engineering.
Tom has gained substantial transfer pricing experience in all kinds of intercompany transactions within groups operating in a wide scope of industries. As a senior consultant at TP&amp;amp;C, Tom identified and addressed potential compliance risks while optimizing the structuring of clients&amp;rsquo; cross-border transactions. He conducted customized economic analyses and documentation strategies to develop pragmatic transfer pricing systems at arm&amp;rsquo;s length.</description></item></channel></rss>